Finding Aid for the Allegra Fuller Snyder papers, 1960-2010 LSC.1881
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Personal Organizational Files, 1960-2010
  - Lundquist, Laurie., 2006 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Luttmann, Gail J., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Correspondence about dance field work in Alaska.
  - Macdonald, Annette C., 1967-2006 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Dance Films Association NEA synopsis of documentary film of Jack Cole. AFS on Advisory Committee. Princeton Book Company Royalty report for Mary Wigman co- written book. Bank account for Macdonald and Snyder. Birthday card. Correspondence. Postcard SAG photo.
  - MacKay, Anne., 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    "Wolf Girls at Vassar: Gay and lesbian experiences 1930-1990." Poetry.
  - Madeira School., 1967-1997 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Update letters of fellow classmates. "Madeira Class of 1945 Fiftieth Reunion Booklet." "Women and Sports: The mind-body connection." 1967 Alumnae Directory.
  - Mahoney, Margaret E., 1984-2007 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Letter explaining that Harkness Fellow Matthew Lloyd was not accepted to UCLA.
  - Maletic, Vera., 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    CV. "Videodance-Technology-Attitude Shift." "Toward a Multidimensional Dance Education." "Laban Concepts and Laban Dialects: Issues of shape." "Laban-Based Terminology: Some historical considerations." Letter of recommendation.
  - Malone, Marjorie., 1993-2003 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Esalen Institute registration form. Taos Art Association "Passages" articles. Correspondence. "The Abuelos of the Taos Valley." "Taos Midwinter Masquerades." Print of Malone painting.
  - Malpede, John., 2007 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Articles about the Los Angeles Poverty Department helping to end homelessness. WAC flyer about activist art making taught by theater director and actor.
  - Manning, Susan Allene., 1984 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Letter about dissertation.
  - Maples, Wendy., 1992 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Maquet, Jacques., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    "Art by Metamorphosis." "Introduction to Aesthetic Anthropology."
  - Maracci, Carmelita., 1961-2008 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Dance Magazine article about Maracci. "The Portrait-The individual voice." Postcard. Photocopied correspondence to Maracci from St. Denis and Ted Shawn. 1990 "Bookman's Weekly for the Specialist Book World." Package with 1946 "Carnegie Hall" program, 1949 Carmelita Maracci at Royce Hall program, flyer, photocopied 1942 and 1949 newspaper articles, five b/w 8x10 and one b/w 4x6 photos. Elspeth Kuang brochure.
  - Marks, Victoria., 1998-2007 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    "Not About Iraq" and "Father/Daughter Dance and Men" UCLA programs. Correspondence.
  - Marshall, Margalit Oved., 1973-2003 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Articles and photocopied articles. Margalit Dance Theatre Company brochure. Letter of recommendation. Statement of Plans.
  - Marshall, Ronald Yao., 1998 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Memorial programs.
  - Maruyama, Magoroh., 1970s? (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Photocopies of "Paradigmatology and its Application to Cross- Disciplinary, Cross-Professional and Cross-Cultural Communication" and "Mindscapes, Social Patterns and Future Development of Scientific Theory Types."
  - Mason, Rona., 1987 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Greeting card and letter.
  - Mattingly, Meagan., 2002 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Letters which include small original art works. Letter of recommendation.
  - Maurine, Camille., 2002 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    "Open Secrets" program. "The Essential Feminine in the World: Salons for women of influence."
  - May, Olivia A., 2007-2009 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    Letter of recommendation for her granddaughter. Story about Olivia. Email from Sam May. "Ambrosia 2007 Epic" includes Olivia poem.
  - McAbee, Phillip., 1994-1998 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    Letters. CV. "Proposal and Implementation Plans."
  - McCauley, Jann., undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Brochure with fee schedule.
  - McClain, Margy., 1995 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Letter and Book Prospectus.
  - McCormick, Malcolm., 1996-2002 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Letters. "Magical Evocation of Paris Ballet."
  - McHale, Magda Cordell., 1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Photocopied "A Painter at Heart" article.
  - McLaughlin, Deborah., 1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Kealiinohomoku Memorial Research Choreographer-in-Residence application. CV.
  - McLuhan, Herbert Marshall., 1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    "Marshall McLuhand Center on Global Communications" program for distinguished teacher awards. Letter from Mary McLuhan.
  - McNally, Terry., 2004 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Regarding AFS interview about Buckminster Fuller for KPFK.
  - Merriam, Alan (1 of 2)., 1964-1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    "Toward a Theory for Ethnomusicology" article used in Ethnic Arts 190. "The Arts and Anthropology." Correspondence.
  - Merriam, Alan (2 of 2)., 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    One b/w 3x4 photo. Correspondence.
  - Messiaen, Olivier., 1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Metzger, Deena and Myerhoff, Barbara., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    "Dear Diary."
  - Meyerhoff, Bill., 1994? (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Milestone Films., 2003 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    2004 DVD and VHS catalog.
  - Miller, Richard., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Milliken, Gary., 2007 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    "Richard Buckminster Fuller: A transcendentalist's trajectory."
  - Mitoma, Judy Susilo., 2001 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Spring UCLA Magazine.
  - Moeller, Peter., 1979 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    "An Opinion by Peter Moeller," a letter to Hugh Hefner. Two poems.
  - Moore, Donald G., 1996 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Moore, Roslyn Elizabeth., 1990-1999 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    CV and cover letter for costume designer/assistant professor. Letter of recommendation.
  - Morales, Sylvia Esther and Morales Hoffman, Lydia E., 1981-1991 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    CVs and letters of recommendation from others.
  - Mori, May., 1990 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    Letter. "Personal History of Fujiko Fujima" and "Personal History of Rankei Fujima."
  - Morley, Christopher., 1967-1998 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    "Christopher Morley on Long Island." Knothole Association Newsletters. Letters.
  - Morley Cochrane, Louise., 1988-2010 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Morris, Mark., 1992-1998 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Morrow, Scott Douglas (Nana Kwasi)., 1992-1998 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    Photocopied newspaper articles about Scott Morrow Dance Theatre and his being named as the chief in the Kwamang area of Ghana.
  - Moving IDEA Company., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    Sixth anniversary program. Claudia Chapline, director.
  - Moving Space Company., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    Photocopied "Moving Space Comes Home" article. Marcia Sakamoto, director.
  - Moiseyev, Igor., 2007 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Mullin, Hilda Hoppe (1 of 2)., 1969-2005 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Letters. Dialogue with Dancers. "Shadow of the Warsaw Ghetto" project plan. Memorial program. 1972 Pacific Oaks College catalog. Letter of recommendation. "Summary Report on Symposium on Theatre for Seniors." Living Arts with Family Environment Center. Dance and early childhood writings. Newsclippings. 1971 "Experiments in Art and Technology Los Angeles."
  - Mullin, Hilda Hoppe (2 of 2)., 1971-1999 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Proposal for "Experimental / Technological Choreography in Los Angeles." "The Cultural Arts for Prevention and Rehabilitation of Drug Abuser." Family Environment Center Annual Report 1987.
  - Mullin, Kathleen., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Notes on a conversation with AFS.
  - Murname, Bridget., 1991-1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Correspondence. Resume. "The Black Boots" film flyer. April/May 1991 "Harvard Film Archive Bulletin."
  - Nadler, Buddy., 1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Correspondence. "The Future of WWWork Project." "Who Will Work in Cyberspace?" written for Ethnic Arts 190A class.
  - Nathanson, Norbert H., 2005 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - National Association of Schools of Dance (NASD)., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Prospectus "Concerning the Formation of a National Association of Schools of Dance."
  - National Dance Institute., 1999 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Summer magazine.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-FY 1986., 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Panelist information, lists, and forms FY 1986.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-FY 1985., 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Panelist information, lists, and forms FY 1985.
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)-Expansion Arts., 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Winter "Expansion Arts Now." Application guidelines FY 1995 and 1996.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-AFS 1980 -1981. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    AFS's NEH 1980-1981 application "Pueblo, People and Performances: The role of dance in Los Angeles history."
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-AFS 1983-1984., 1982 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Requests for letters of recommendation for 1983-1984 Fellowships for Independent Study and Research and for College Teachers. No proposal included. Correspondence.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Asian Performing Arts 1979., 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    Summer Seminar Program on Asian Performing Arts at UCLA.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Cohen, Selma Jeanne 1977. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    NEH application for "International Encyclopedia of Dance."
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Cohen, Selma Jeanne 1978. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Submitted forms to AFS for evaluation.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Fellowships for College Teachers., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    AFS panelist information FY 1981-1982.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Fellowships and Seminars Panel., 1987 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    AFS panelist information FY 1988-1989.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Hauser, Rick., 1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    AFS panelist information "Myth/A Television Series." Note to AFS. Proposal FY 1985.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-de Panizza Lorch, Maristella., 1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    AFS panelist information "The Renaissance Theater in Northern Italy: The court and the city (1400-1600), November 14-18, 1978." Proposal FY 1978.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Museums and Historical Organizations Programs., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Lists for grants made in fiscal years 1977, 1978, and 1979.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Povey, John F., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    AFS as joint principal investigator for "African Humanities Videotape." Proposal FY 1980.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Robinson, Beverly Ethnic Arts., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Application for "Applying the Arts for Social Change." Proposal FY 1983 -1984. "Ethnic Arts as a Major" brochure.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-Smoliar, Stephen W., 1978 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    AFS panelist information. No proposal or title included.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)-UCLA., 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Correspondence and documentation for Summer Seminar for College Teachers on Asian Performing Arts at UCLA. Final performance reports for 1979 and 1981.
  - National Initiative to Preserve America's Dance (NIPAD)., 1994-2000 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    "Save as: Dance." Correspondence with AFS as Advisory Reviewer. Project Narratives to be reviewed by AFS. Sept. 1999, May 2000, Dec. 2000, Feb. 2001 "Next Steps" which focuses on documentation and preservation issue of dance. "Guidelines and Application Packet-Cycle II-1995."
  - National Resource Centre for Dance (NRCD)., 1985-1999 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    Autumn 1985, 1988-1989, Sept. 1998-Aug. 1999 services and publications catalogs.
  - Neel, Darlene., 2000 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Nef, Evelyn Stefansson., 2002 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Newman, Deena., 1992-1998 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    CVs. Letters to AFS concerning grant and job applications.
  - New York City Ballet., 1952-2006 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Jan. 2006 "Playbill." Winter 2006 repertory lists. Tanaquil Le Clercq obituary. Newspaper clippings. Photocopy of Dec. 1986 The New York "Profiles: Conversations with Kirstein-I" article. Dec. 1998 Vanity Fair "Blanchine's Dream" article. "Dance for a City: 50 years of the New York City Ballet" packet. Brochures. John Taras obituary.
  - New York University., 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Course descriptions.
  - Nijinsky, Vaslav., 1987-1998 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Newsclippings. Kyra Nijinsky obituary.
  - Noguchi, Isamu., 1988-2001 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Isamu Noguchi Garden Museum brochures. Vitra Design Museum brochure. Newsclippings. Japanese American National Museum catalogue of "Isamu Noguchi and Modern Japanese Ceramics." "Design Within Reach" brochure.
  - North, Marion., 1998 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Letters from The Future of Dance, Laban Centre, London.
  - Nueva., 1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Photocopy of the Nueva Model of Education philosophy statement.
  - Obama, Barack., 2009 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Printout of Obama's Inaugural Address.
  - Oberstein, Liz., 1980-1992 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Obituaries., 2009 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Larry Halprin, Gerald Myers, Arthur Snyder, Chris P. Rosenfeld, Sy Wexler, William Murray, Marian van Tuyl, IMDb of George Justin, Clifford Geertz, Monica Moseley.
  - O'Connor, Donald., 1987 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    The Christian Science Monitor clipping.
  - Oligny, Donna S., 1978 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Photocopy of memorial notice and speech.
  - Olsson, Carin Maria Cecilia., 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Letters. CV.
  - Ortiz, Alfonso., 1988 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    Summer "Indian Affairs."
  - Pacific Asia Museum., 1998 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    AFS on Advisors' Council.
  - Pacifica Graduate Institute., undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    Photocopied brochure.
  - Padfield, Marsha., 1989-1997 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Palmer, Cathy Agnew., 1990s (Box 23, Folder 20)
    South West Scotland Screen Commission card, brochure, flyer.
  - Pavlova, Anna., 1923 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    Original 1923 Anna Pavlova (spelled Pavlowa) program at Manhattan Opera House.
  - Pearce, Celia and Peter., 1995-2001 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    Letters. March 1996 "intermediaWORLD" program and directory. Charles Ostman informationals. Celia's resume. "The Ins & Outs of Non-Linear Storytelling." Brochures for Peter Jon Pearce's Steelcase chair 'Cachet'.
  - Pepperdine, Warren., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    "Toward an Understanding of How a Society Uses Theatre to Transmit Cultural Values."
  - Perez, Rudy., 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    "Rudy Perez-Los Angeles, 1980" by Naima Prevots. "Smart Moves: Rudy Perez" by Jacki Apple.
  - Perron, Wendy., 1999 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    Paragraph describing Perron from the Alpert Foundation.
  - Persson, Lorraine., undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    Press release about her dance company's debut.
  - Pew Charitable Trust., 1999 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    New York Times "Heavyweight Foundation Throws Itself Behind Idea of a Cultural Policy" article.
  - Phillips, Miriam., 1991-2008 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    "D'mba: As a dance event-A dance ethnologist's perspective." CVs. Correspondence including job application recommendations.
  - Pike, Kenneth L., 1954 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    "Towards a Theory of the Structure of Human Behavior." "Emic and Etic Standpoints for the Description of Behavior."
  - Piker, Joan., 1994-2002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Cornwall Bridge Pottery brochure. Letters. 50th wedding anniversary notice. 1994 Computer History Association of California Newsletters. Myron Piker memorial notice and program.
  - Pilobolus., undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Photocopy of "The Ennui and the Ecstasy" article.
  - Pogofsky-Harris, Elisse., 1992-2003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Promotional postcards. Newsclipping. Frye Art Museum flyer.
  - Pong, Chua Soo., 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Correspondence. Seameo Regional Centre for Archaeology and Fine Arts of the Southeast Asian Ministers of Education Organization.
  - Potter, Walker., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    The New Yorker "With the Potters" article.
  - Press, Carol., 1991 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Pritzker Award., 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Brochure and program for Jose Rafael Moneo. Pritzker book for Tadao Ando (water damaged).
  - Protetch, Max., 1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Quigley, Colin Harding., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Dissertation abstract. 1990 bibliography. Photocopies of selected writings.
  - Quintin, Jonathan., undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    "Sacred Geometry: Multi-media color light show" flyer.
  - Racy, A. Jihad., undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    Music 290 reading list "Music and Ecstasy."
  - Raftis, Alkis., 1965-1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    "Greek Dances: Theatre Dora Stratou" brochure. Letters. Booklets. "Shared Tasks and Communal Celebrations in Rural Greece." "Scientific Research and Publication on Dance in Greece." "A Systems Theory Approach to the Study of Dance- Related Social Activities." "Dance in Greece."
  - Ralston Pahr, Jane., 1992 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Yoga Moves. "Dance-The Roots of Eternity."
  - Rauschenberg. Robert., 2005 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Exhibit program for Hoarfrosts at Guild Hall.
  - Ravarou, Adrian., 1993-1996 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Letter. "Dance as an Energy Transformer." Card of complaint about admissions information from Dance Department.
  - Rea Bailey, Shiva., 1994 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    Forrest Yoga Circle flyers and letters. Application for Graduate Study in Dance Movement Therapy.
  - Reel-Rreal / Real-Reel., undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
    "Real Art?" by Ellen Searle.
  - Reineck, Janet., 1991-2001 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    University application essay. Book forward that includes Albanian village descriptions. CV. Letter of recommendation.
  - Reinking, Mark., 1992, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    Winter 1995 "Financial Outlook." Photocopy of book cover "Lemuria - The Lost Continent of the Pacific."
  - Rele, Kanak., 1980 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Renouf, Renee., 1989-1998 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - ReRead., 1999 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    Ashley Peterson's organization that redistributes used magazines to homeless.
  - Reynolds, Mary Stephanie., 1990 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Job application material. "Dance Brings About Everything: Dance power in the Northern Ute and Anglo Mormon philosophies of dance."
  - Reynolds, Newell Taylor., 2007 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    Obituary of Bella Lewitzky's husband.
  - Reynolds, William C., 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    Correspondence. "Scientific Criteria for Judging Human Movement Notation Systems." "Where Do We Start in Describing a Dance Event?" Fall ICTM Dance Newsletter.
  - Riefenstahl, Leni., 2002 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    Los Angeles Times article.
  - Ries, Frank W. D., 1986 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    "Scholarship and Musical Theatre." "Sammy Lee: The Broadway career." "Sammy Lee: The Hollywood career."
  - Rigler, Jaime., 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    "Conserving Television's Richness." "Classic Arts Showcase Channels Eclectic Programs."
  - Rinzler, Kate Hughes., 1994-2002 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    Ralph C. Rinzler obituary. Batik painting exhibit programs. Fall 1994 "Talk Story: Center for Folklife Programs and Cultural Studies."
  - Riverside University of California Dance., 1990 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    Agenda and meeting minutes for Intercampus for MA in Dance History.
  - Robbins, Jerome., 1989-1999 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    Newsclippings. "Q & A with Deborah Jowitt" author of biography of Robbins.
  - Robinson, Alfred., 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Correspondence. "In Intimacy with the Spirit: Symbols of sustenance, suffering, stillness and completion in the Yaqui Deer Dance and the Christian Passion." "Beneath the Mask of the Pahkola: Survival, continuity and renaissance in the body of Yaqui tradition."
  - Robinson, Beverly J., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Interview about "Culture and the African Diaspora."
  - Rochlein, Harvey., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    "Notes on Contemporary American Dance."
  - Rodrigue, Jean-Louis., 2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    "Teaching Actors to Move with the Gracefulness of Dancers."
  - Rodriguez, Angela Moya., 1980s-2006 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Letters. Photos and brief bio of the founder of Latino Theatre Company.
  - Rodriguez, Sylvia., 1997 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Romero-Hymer, Brenda., 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Rosellini, Jim Talle., 1988 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    CV. African Family Films Guggenheim Foundation application.
  - Rosenberg, Sam., 1992-2002 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Photo. Letter from daughter Amber Sabri. Obituary.
  - Rosenfeld, Eugene., 1999 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Memorial writing.
  - Ross, Bertram., 2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Performance newspaper notice.
  - Ross, Herbert., undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Program for kick-off celebration of the Lewitzky Dance Company's final season.
  - Royce, Anya Peterson., 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Correspondence. "New Directions in the Anthropology of Dance."
  - Rubin, Arnold., 1988 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Russell, Beverly., 1995 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    "Harmony By Design: The golden mean as a design tool" booklet and flyer by Rachel Fletcher.
  - Rutan, Raymond A., 1980 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Statement of proposed activity.
  - Ruyter, Nancy Lee., 1980 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Sadoff, Elizabeth., undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    12 person exhibit "Drawn to the Line" brochure.
  - Sanders, Mary Lee., 1996-2003 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    "Of Wolves and Women: Dreamed, danced and remembered." Photocopied photos. Cards.
  - Sanford, Terry., 1998 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Sarabhai, Mallika-Darpana., 1998 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    Aug.-Oct. Darpana Academy Newsletter.
  - Santorio, Angiola., 1957, 1991-1995 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    Obituary. "White Earth Land Recovery Project: 1993 Year end report." "Profiles in the Outlaw Area" about Buckminster Fuller and Maorian Keeper of the Chants. Letters. 1990, 1991, 1992 Institute of World Culture meetings.
  - Scalin, Judy., 1999 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    National Dance Education Organization report.
  - Schechner, Richard., 1980 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    "Actuals: A look into performance theory" used in Ethnic Arts 190
  - Schiller, Gretchen Klein., 1991-1998 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    Letters. Photocopied newsclipping. CV. "Danse Visions: Festival International de cine-video-danse" program. Wedding photos. Grant application for "7 Women in a Dress-a video-dance." Resume. Portfolio.
  - Schiller, Tom., 2003 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Schindler, Sammi., 1999 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    Flyers for "Moving With Spirit" retreats and celebrations.
  - Schlossberg, Edwin., 1994, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    SonyWonder Technology Lab brochure. dESIgn screen savers. Letter. Article about being Buckminster Fuller's protégé.
  - Schneider, Gretchen., 1978-2006 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    Resume. "Holes-Gaps-Connections" exhibit postcard. Letter.
  - Schonberg, Bessie., 1997 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Schwerin, Doris., 2006-2007 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    Letter. Poem.
  - Scott, Chloe., 1998, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    "Dancing Queen: At 80, dancer Chloe Scott is still on her toes" article. Letter with essay "The Last Time I Saw My Father He Was Dancing."
  - Scott Rosalsky, Marion-Memorial., 2009 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    June 14th memorial program draft. Mailing lists. Note from Doris Siegel. Photocopy of 1954 New Dance Group program that included Donald McKayle, Maslow, Sodolow. 1965 photo titled "Marion Scott, professional name of Marion Goldberg Rosalsky." Correspondence among memorial people. Pearl Lang obituary. Carl Edward Patrick memorial program. Program for "Anyone Home: Reunion tour" dedicated to Marion Scott. Winter UCLA Emeriti Newsletter.
  - Scott Rosalsky, Marion-Spirit Dances (1 of 2)., 1999-2007 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Brochures. Promotional flyers and postcards. AFS greeting card. Obituary. Correspondence. Newsclippings.
  - Scott Rosalsky, Marion-Spirit Dances (2 of 2)., 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)